{
	"allQuestions": [{
		"id": 59,
		"question": "Which animal is known as the (Ship of the Desert)?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Camel", "Dog", "Horse", "Lion"],
		"correctAnswer": "Camel"
	}, {
		"id": 60,
		"question": "How many hours are there in 1 day?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["20 hours", "24 hours", "23 hours", "22 hours"],
		"correctAnswer": "24 hours"
	}, {
		"id": 61,
		"question": "How many days are there in 1 week?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["5 days", "8 days", "7 days", "6 days"],
		"correctAnswer": "7 days"
	}, {
		"id": 62,
		"question": "How many letters are there in the English alphabet?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["20 letters", "25 letters", "24 letters", "26 letters"],
		"correctAnswer": "26 letters"
	}, {
		"id": 63,
		"question": "How many colours a rainbow have?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["7 colours", "3 colours", "5 colours", "6 colours"],
		"correctAnswer": "7 colours"
	}, {
		"id": 64,
		"question": "How many days are there in one year?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["350 days", "365 days", "360 days", "355 days"],
		"correctAnswer": "365 days"
	}, {
		"id": 65,
		"question": "How many minutes are there in one hour?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["60 minutes", "30 minutes", "40 minutes", "70 minutes"],
		"correctAnswer": "60 minutes"
	}, {
		"id": 66,
		"question": "How many centimetre are there in one meter? ",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["10 cm", "100 cm", "1000 cm", "1 cm"],
		"correctAnswer": "100 cm"
	}, {
		"id": 67,
		"question": "How may meters in one kilometer?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["100 m", "500 m", "1000 m", "10 m"],
		"correctAnswer": "1000 m"
	}, {
		"id": 68,
		"question": "How many consonants are there in the English alphabet?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["20", "22", "24", "21"],
		"correctAnswer": "21"
	}, {
		"id": 69,
		"question": "How many vowels are there in the English alphabet?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["5 vowels ", "7 vowels ", "8 vowels ", "4 vowels "],
		"correctAnswer": "5 vowels "
	}, {
		"id": 70,
		"question": "Which animal is not a pet commonly?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["A Dog", "A Cat", "A Goat", "A Lion"],
		"correctAnswer": "A Lion"
	}, {
		"id": 71,
		"question": "Find the uncommon one?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Dog", "Cat", "Goat", "Shark"],
		"correctAnswer": "Shark"
	}, {
		"id": 72,
		"question": "Find the uncommon one?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Cricket", "Golf", "Footbal", "Kabaddi"],
		"correctAnswer": "Kabaddi"
	}, {
		"id": 73,
		"question": "Find the uncommon one?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Car", "Mobile", "Cycle", "Bus"],
		"correctAnswer": "Mobile"
	}, {
		"id": 74,
		"question": "Animal normally known as.. King of the Jungle",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Tiger", "Fox", "Lion", "Elephant"],
		"correctAnswer": "Lion"
	}, {
		"id": 75,
		"question": "Capital of India?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Mumbai", "New Delhi", "Gandhinagar", "Bihar"],
		"correctAnswer": "New Delhi"
	}, {
		"id": 76,
		"question": "Find the uncommon one?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["India", "China", "US", "Bhopal"],
		"correctAnswer": "Bhopal"
	}, {
		"id": 77,
		"question": "Find the uncommon one?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Orange", "Green", "Blue", "Fish"],
		"correctAnswer": "Fish"
	}, {
		"id": 78,
		"question": "National animal of India",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Tiger", "Elephant", "Horse", "Lion"],
		"correctAnswer": "Tiger"
	}, {
		"id": 79,
		"question": "National birt of India?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Peacock", "Pigeon", "Sparrow", "Eagle"],
		"correctAnswer": "Peacock"
	}, {
		"id": 80,
		"question": "National flower of India?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Rose", "Lotus", "Lily", "Sunflower"],
		"correctAnswer": "Lotus"
	}, {
		"id": 81,
		"question": "National fruit of India?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Orange", "Apple", "Banana", "Mango"],
		"correctAnswer": "Mango"
	}, {
		"id": 82,
		"question": "Name the primary colours?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Red, Yellow and Blue", "Green, Orange and Red", "Blue, White and Gray", "Green, Red and White"],
		"correctAnswer": "Red, Yellow and Blue"
	}, {
		"id": 83,
		"question": "Smallest month of the year?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["March", "February", "October", "April"],
		"correctAnswer": "February"
	}, {
		"id": 84,
		"question": "Who was the first Prime Minister of India?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Indira Gandhi", "Mahatma Gandhi", "Sardar Vallabhbhai Patel ", "Pandit Jawaharlal Nehru"],
		"correctAnswer": "Pandit Jawaharlal Nehru"
	}, {
		"id": 85,
		"question": "Which festival is called the festival of colours?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Diwali", "Holi", "Lohri", "Rakhi"],
		"correctAnswer": "Holi"
	}, {
		"id": 86,
		"question": "The national aquatic animal of India?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["River Dolphin", "White cheeked shark", "Starfish", "Goldfish"],
		"correctAnswer": "River Dolphin"
	}, {
		"id": 87,
		"question": "The planet known as the Red Planet?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Mercury", "Earth", "Jupiter", "Mars"],
		"correctAnswer": "Mars"
	}, {
		"id": 88,
		"question": "The country known as the Land of the Rising Sun?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Japan", "India", "USA", "Hong Kong"],
		"correctAnswer": "Japan"
	}, {
		"id": 89,
		"question": "How many millimeters are there in a centimeters?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["15mm", "20mm", "1mm", "10mm"],
		"correctAnswer": "10mm"
	}, {
		"id": 90,
		"question": "Name the hardest substance available on Earth?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Diamond", "Gold", "Iron", "Silver"],
		"correctAnswer": "Diamond"
	}, {
		"id": 91,
		"question": "Name the shape that has ten sides?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Octagon", "Decagon", "Polygon", "Hexagon"],
		"correctAnswer": "Decagon"
	}, {
		"id": 167,
		"question": "Who is Sachine Tandulkar?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["A Cricketer", "A Golfer", "A Singer", "A Dancer"],
		"correctAnswer": "A Cricketer"
	}, {
		"id": 338,
		"question": "Nick name of \"Dibrugarh\"?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Silk City", "Tea City Of India", "Steel capital Of India", "City Of Rallies"],
		"correctAnswer": "Tea City Of India"
	}, {
		"id": 339,
		"question": "Nickname of \"Hajipur\"?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Silk City", "The City Of Blood", "Bananas City", "Green City"],
		"correctAnswer": "Bananas City"
	}, {
		"id": 340,
		"question": "\"Kurukshetra\" is known as?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["City Of Lakes", "Queen Of Hills", "Land Of Arecanut", "City Of Mahabharata"],
		"correctAnswer": "City Of Mahabharata"
	}, {
		"id": 341,
		"question": "\"Guwahati\" is known as:",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["The Land Of Leechi", "Gateway Of Bastar", "Gateway Of North East India", "Textile City Of India"],
		"correctAnswer": "Gateway Of North East India"
	}, {
		"id": 342,
		"question": "\"Bhagalpur\" is know as:",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Silk City", "Bananas City", "Rice Bowl Of India", "City Of Rallies"],
		"correctAnswer": "Silk City"
	}, {
		"id": 343,
		"question": "\"Gaya\" is known as:",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Gateway Of Bastar", "Green City", "Mini Lahasa", "The City Of Enlightenment"],
		"correctAnswer": "The City Of Enlightenment"
	}, {
		"id": 344,
		"question": "\"Muzaffarpur\" is also called:",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Steel capital Of India", "The Land Of Leechi", "Gateway Of Bastar", "City Of Rallies"],
		"correctAnswer": "The Land Of Leechi"
	}, {
		"id": 345,
		"question": "\"Nalanda\" is also know as:",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["The Land Of Leechi", "Rice Bowl Of India", "Land Of Knowledge", "Butter City"],
		"correctAnswer": "Land Of Knowledge"
	}, {
		"id": 346,
		"question": "Which city is known as \"City Of Rallies\"?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Bhopal ", "New Delhi", "Mumbai", "Pune"],
		"correctAnswer": "New Delhi"
	}, {
		"id": 347,
		"question": "Which city is known as \"Cleanest City Of India\"?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Mumbai", "Cheenai", "Indore", "Jabalpur"],
		"correctAnswer": "Indore"
	}, {
		"id": 348,
		"question": "Which city is known as \"Mini Mumbai\"?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Pune", "Bhopal", "Indore", "Gandhinagar"],
		"correctAnswer": "Indore"
	}, {
		"id": 349,
		"question": "Which city is know as \"Power Hub City\"?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Indore", "Jalgaon", "Bhopal", "Mundi"],
		"correctAnswer": "Mundi"
	}, {
		"id": 350,
		"question": "Where \"Gateway Of India\" is present?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Mumbai", "Nasik", "Cuttack", "Pondicherry"],
		"correctAnswer": "Mumbai"
	}, {
		"id": 351,
		"question": "Where \"Red Fort\" is present?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Delhi", "Bikaner", "Udaipur", "Jodhpur"],
		"correctAnswer": "Delhi"
	}, {
		"id": 352,
		"question": "Which place is known as \"Yoga Capital Of The World\"?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Shimla", "Mathura", "Agra", "Rishikesh"],
		"correctAnswer": "Rishikesh"
	}, {
		"id": 353,
		"question": "Which place is known as \"Silver City\"?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Puri", "Cuttack", "Bikaner", "Bikaner"],
		"correctAnswer": "Cuttack"
	}, {
		"id": 354,
		"question": "\"Taj Mahal\" is present in which city in India?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Delhi", "Agra", "Pune", "Indore"],
		"correctAnswer": "Agra"
	}, {
		"id": 355,
		"question": "\"Qutab Minar\" is present in which city in India?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Delhi", "Riapur", "Juna", "Agra"],
		"correctAnswer": "Delhi"
	}, {
		"id": 356,
		"question": "\"Charminar\" is present in which city in India?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Hyderabad", "Nasik", "Pune", "Mumbai"],
		"correctAnswer": "Hyderabad"
	}, {
		"id": 357,
		"question": "\"India Gate\" is present in which city in India?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Goa", "Jaipur", "Delhi", "Mumbai"],
		"correctAnswer": "Delhi"
	}, {
		"id": 358,
		"question": "\"Lotus Temple\" is present in which city in India?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Amritsar", "Guna", "Delhi", "Jaipur"],
		"correctAnswer": "Delhi"
	}, {
		"id": 359,
		"question": "\"Jama Masjid\" is present in which city in India?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Bhopal", "Alibagh", "Pune", "Delhi"],
		"correctAnswer": "Delhi"
	}, {
		"id": 360,
		"question": "\"Golden Temple\" is present in which city in India?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Lahor", "Delhi", "Amritsar", "Mumbai"],
		"correctAnswer": "Amritsar"
	}, {
		"id": 361,
		"question": "\"Amer Fort\" is present in which city in India?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Jaipur", "Jabalpur", "Kota", "Mandu"],
		"correctAnswer": "Jaipur"
	}, {
		"id": 362,
		"question": "\"City Palace\" is present in which city in India?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Udaipur", "Raipur", "Jaipur", "Delhi"],
		"correctAnswer": "Udaipur"
	}, {
		"id": 363,
		"question": "\"Hawa Mahal\" is present in which city in India?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Jaipur", "Udaipur", "Chhatapur", "Bhopal"],
		"correctAnswer": "Jaipur"
	}, {
		"id": 364,
		"question": "Where \"Udayagiri\" is present?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Bhubaneswar", "Gwalior", "Delhi", "Bishnupur"],
		"correctAnswer": "Bhubaneswar"
	}, {
		"id": 365,
		"question": "Where \"Sun Temple Konark\" is present?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Aurangabad", "Hampi", "Puri", "Pavagadh"],
		"correctAnswer": "Puri"
	}, {
		"id": 366,
		"question": "Where \"Khajuraho\" is present?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Hampi", "Chennai", "Kahjuraho", "Sanchi"],
		"correctAnswer": "Kahjuraho"
	}, {
		"id": 367,
		"question": "Where \"Ajanta Caves\" is present?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Leh", "Aurangabad", "Agra", "Hampi"],
		"correctAnswer": "Aurangabad"
	}, {
		"id": 368,
		"question": "Where \"Ellora Caves\" is present?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Aurangabad", "Chennai", "Hampi", "Mumbai"],
		"correctAnswer": "Aurangabad"
	}, {
		"id": 369,
		"question": "Where \"Chola Temples\" is present?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Pattadakal", "Chennai", "New Delhi", "Pune"],
		"correctAnswer": "Chennai"
	}, {
		"id": 370,
		"question": "Where \"Pattadakal monuments\" is present?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Pattadakal", "Agra", "Hyderabad", "Leh"],
		"correctAnswer": "Pattadakal"
	}, {
		"id": 371,
		"question": "Where \"Statue of Unity\" is present?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Kevadiya", "Navsari", "Surat", "Pune"],
		"correctAnswer": "Kevadiya"
	}, {
		"id": 372,
		"question": "Where \"Rajarani Temple\" is present?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Alibag", "Bhubaneswar", "Pune", "Hyderabad"],
		"correctAnswer": "Bhubaneswar"
	}, {
		"id": 373,
		"question": "Where \"Kolaba Fort\" is present?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Goa", "Vaishali", "Alibag", "Pune"],
		"correctAnswer": "Alibag"
	}, {
		"id": 374,
		"question": "Where \"Golkonda Fort\" is present?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Mumbai", "Hyderabad", "Pune", "New Delhi"],
		"correctAnswer": "Hyderabad"
	}, {
		"id": 375,
		"question": "Where \"Jageshwar Temples\" is present?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Hassan", "Hampi", "Almora", "Sivasagar"],
		"correctAnswer": "Almora"
	}, {
		"id": 376,
		"question": "Where \"Rani Roopmati Mahal\" is present?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Indore", "Mandu", "Lonavala", "Pune"],
		"correctAnswer": "Mandu"
	}, {
		"id": 377,
		"question": "Where \"Jahaj Mahal\" is present?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Mandu", "Bhopal", "Pune", "Indore"],
		"correctAnswer": "Mandu"
	}, {
		"id": 378,
		"question": "Where \"Fort of Kalinjar\" is present?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Pune", "Bhopal", "Kanpur", "Hassan"],
		"correctAnswer": "Kanpur"
	}, {
		"id": 379,
		"question": "Where \"Durga Temple\" is present?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Aihole", "Hassan", "Bijapur", "Udhampur"],
		"correctAnswer": "Aihole"
	}, {
		"id": 380,
		"question": "Where \"Ibrahim Rouza\" is present?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Pune", "Ajmer", "Hampi", "Bijapur"],
		"correctAnswer": "Bijapur"
	}, {
		"id": 381,
		"question": "Where \"Rambagh\" is present?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Udaipur", "Agra", "Pune", "Lucknow"],
		"correctAnswer": "Agra"
	}, {
		"id": 382,
		"question": "Where \"Rani Mahar is present?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Hampi", "Bharatpur", "Jhansi", "Sholapur"],
		"correctAnswer": "Jhansi"
	}, {
		"id": 383,
		"question": "Where \"Hidimba Devi Temple\" is present?",
		"category": "gk",
		"answer": ["Leh", "Pune", "Manali", "Goa"],
		"correctAnswer": "Manali"
	}]
}
